Guide to the Joint Western Area Committee Records, 1965-2004 LAC0003
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- JWAC August 1981 [9/34], 1981 August (Box 48, Folder 4)
  Agenda Meeting August 10-15, 1981, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1981 [10/34], 1981 August (Box 48, Folder 5)
- JWAC August 1981 [11/34], 1981 August (Box 48, Folder 6)
  Main Committee, OTR Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1981 [12/34], 1981 August (Box 49, Folder 1)
  Minutes Meeting August 10-14, 1981, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes
- JWAC August 1981 [13/34], 1981 August (Box 49, Folder 2)
- JWAC August 1981 [14/34], 1981 August (Box 49, Folder 3)
  Main Committee, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1981 [15/34], 1981 August (Box 49, Folder 4)
- JWAC August 1981 [16/34], 1981 August (Box 49, Folder 5)
- JWAC August 1981 [17/34], 1981 August (Box 49, Folder 6)
- JWAC August 1981 [18/34], 1981 August (Box 50, Folder 1)
- JWAC August 1981 [19/34], 1981 August (Box 50, Folder 2)
  Transcripts/Proceedings of the Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes
- JWAC August 1981 [20/34], 1981 August (Box 50, Folder 3)
- JWAC August 1981 [21/34], 1981 August (Box 50, Folder 4)
- JWAC August 1981 [22/34], 1981 August (Box 50, Folder 5)
- JWAC August 1981 [23/34], 1981 August (Box 50, Folder 6)
- JWAC August 1981 [24/34], 1981 August (Box 51, Folder 1)
- JWAC August 1981 [25/34], 1981 August (Box 51, Folder 2)
- JWAC August 1981 [26/34], 1981 August (Box 51, Folder 3)
- JWAC August 1981 [27/34], 1981 August (Box 51, Folder 4)
- JWAC August 1981 [28/34], 1981 August (Box 51, Folder 5)
- JWAC August 1981 [29/34], 1981 August (Box 51, Folder 6)
- JWAC August 1981 [30/34], 1981 August (Box 52, Folder 1)
- JWAC August 1981 [31/34], 1981 August (Box 52, Folder 2)
- JWAC August 1981 [32/34], 1981 August (Box 52, Folder 3)
- JWAC August 1981 [33/34], 1981 August (Box 52, Folder 4)
- JWAC August 1981 [34/34], 1981 August (Box 52, Folder 5)
- JWAC November 1981 [1/24], 1981 November (Box 52, Folder 6)
  Meeting Agenda November 9-13, 1981, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1981 [2/24], 1981 November (Box 53, Folder 1)
- JWAC November 1981 [3/24], 1981 November (Box 53, Folder 2)
  Agenda, Minutes Meeting November 9-13, 1981, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Main Committee, OTR Committee, Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1981 [4/24], 1981 November (Box 53, Folder 3)
  Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Main Committee, OTR Committee, Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1981 [5/24], 1981 November (Box 53, Folder 4)
  Agenda Meeting November 9-13, 1981, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Main Committee, OTR Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1981 [6/24], 1981 November (Box 53, Folder 5)
  Committee for Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries), Minutes of Meeting November 9-13, 1981, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1981 [7/24], 1981 November (Box 53, Folder 6)
- JWAC November 1981 [8/24], 1981 November (Box 54, Folder 1)
  Proceedings/Transcripts Main Committee
- JWAC November 1981 [9/24], 1981 November (Box 54, Folder 2)
- JWAC November 1981 [10/24], 1981 November (Box 54, Folder 3)
- JWAC November 1981 [11/24], 1981 November (Box 54, Folder 4)
- JWAC November 1981 [12/24], 1981 November (Box 54, Folder 5)
  Proceedings/Transcripts Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC November 1981 [13/24], 1981 November (Box 54, Folder 6)
- JWAC November 1981 [14/24], 1981 November (Box 54, Folder 7)
- JWAC November 1981 [15/24], 1981 November (Box 55, Folder 1)
- JWAC November 1981 [16/24], 1981 November (Box 55, Folder 2)
- JWAC November 1981 [17/24], 1981 November (Box 55, Folder 3)
- JWAC November 1981 [18/24], 1981 November (Box 55, Folder 4)
- JWAC November 1981 [19/24], 1981 November (Box 55, Folder 5)
- JWAC November 1981 [20/24], 1981 November (Box 55, Folder 6)
- JWAC November 1981 [21/24], 1981 November (Box 55, Folder 7)
- JWAC November 1981 [22/24], 1981 November (Box 56, Folder 1)
- JWAC November 1981 [23/24], 1981 November (Box 56, Folder 2)
- JWAC November 1981 [24/24], 1981 November (Box 56, Folder 3)
- JWAC February 1982 [1/20], 1982 February (Box 56, Folder 4)
  Agenda, February 15-19, 1982, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1982 [2/20], 1982 February (Box 56, Folder 5)
  Minutes Meeting February 15-19, 1982, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Main Committee, OTR Committee, Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1982 [3/20], 1982 February (Box 56, Folder 6)
  Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Break Bulk Committee, Main Committee, OTR Committee, Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1982 [4/20], 1982 February (Box 57, Folder 1)
- JWAC February 1982 [5/20], 1982 February (Box 57, Folder 2)
  Proceedings of the Main Committee
- JWAC February 1982 [6/20], 1982 February (Box 57, Folder 3)
  Proceedings of the Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC February 1982 [7/20], 1982 February (Box 57, Folder 4)
- JWAC February 1982 [8/20], 1982 February (Box 57, Folder 5)
- JWAC February 1982 [9/20], 1982 February (Box 58, Folder 1)
- JWAC February 1982 [10/20], 1982 February (Box 58, Folder 2)
- JWAC February 1982 [11/20], 1982 February (Box 58, Folder 3)
- JWAC February 1982 [12/20], 1982 February (Box 58, Folder 4)
  Committee for Local Operations
- JWAC February 1982 [13/20], 1982 February (Box 58, Folder 5)
- JWAC February 1982 [14/20], 1982 February (Box 58, Folder 6)
- JWAC February 1982 [15/20], 1982 February (Box 59, Folder 1)
- JWAC February 1982 [16/20], 1982 February (Box 59, Folder 2)
- JWAC February 1982 [17/20], 1982 February (Box 59, Folder 3)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the P&D Break Bulk Committee
- JWAC February 1982 [18/20], 1982 February (Box 59, Folder 4)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters
- JWAC February 1982 [19/20], 1982 February (Box 59, Folder 5)
- JWAC February 1982 [20/20], 1982 February (Box 59, Folder 6)
- JWAC May 1982 [1/26], 1982 May (Box 60, Folder 1)
  Agenda Meeting May 10-17, 1982, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Break Bulk Committee, Office Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1982 [2/26], 1982 May (Box 60, Folder 2)
  Main Committee, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1982 [3/26], 1982 May (Box 60, Folder 3)
  Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Break Bulk Committee, Office Disputes, Main Committee, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1982 [4/26], 1982 May (Box 60, Folder 4)
- JWAC May 1982 [5/26], 1982 May (Box 60, Folder 5)
- JWAC May 1982 [6/26], 1982 May (Box 61, Folder 1)
- JWAC May 1982 [7/26], 1982 May (Box 61, Folder 2)
- JWAC May 1982 [8/26], 1982 May (Box 61, Folder 3)
- JWAC May 1982 [9/26], 1982 May (Box 61, Folder 4)
- JWAC May 1982 [10/26], 1982 May (Box 61, Folder 5)
- JWAC May 1982 [11/26], 1982 May (Box 61, Folder 6)
- JWAC May 1982 [12/26], 1982 May (Box 62, Folder 1)
- JWAC May 1982 [13/26], 1982 May (Box 62, Folder 2)
- JWAC May 1982 [14/26], 1982 May (Box 62, Folder 3)
- JWAC May 1982 [15/26], 1982 May (Box 62, Folder 4)
- JWAC May 1982 [16/26], 1982 May (Box 62, Folder 5)
  Transcripts/Proceedings of the P&D Break Bulk Committee
- JWAC May 1982 [17/26], 1982 May (Box 62, Folder 6)
- JWAC May 1982 [18/26], 1982 May (Box 63, Folder 1)
- JWAC May 1982 [19/26], 1982 May (Box 63, Folder 2)
- JWAC May 1982 [20/26], 1982 May (Box 63, Folder 3)
- JWAC May 1982 [21/26], 1982 May (Box 63, Folder 4)
- JWAC May 1982 [22/26], 1982 May (Box 63, Folder 5)
- JWAC May 1982 [23/26], 1982 May (Box 63, Folder 6)
  Transcripts/Proceedings of the Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters
- JWAC May 1982 [24/26], 1982 May (Box 64, Folder 1)
- JWAC May 1982 [25/26], 1982 May (Box 64, Folder 2)
- JWAC May 1982 [26/26], 1982 May (Box 64, Folder 3)
- JWAC August 1982 [1/23], 1982 August (Box 64, Folder 4)
  Agenda Meeting August 9-13, 1982, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Break Bulk Committee, Office Disputes, Main Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1982 [2/23], 1982 August (Box 64, Folder 5)
  O-T-R Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries); Minutes Meeting August 9-13, 1982, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1982 [3/23], 1982 August (Box 64, Folder 6)
  Break Bulk Committee, Office Disputes, Main Committee, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1982 [4/23], 1982 August (Box 65, Folder 1)
- JWAC August 1982 [5/23], 1982 August (Box 65, Folder 2)
- JWAC August 1982 [6/23], 1982 August (Box 65, Folder 3)
- JWAC August 1982 [7/23], 1982 August (Box 65, Folder 4)
- JWAC August 1982 [8/23], 1982 August (Box 65, Folder 5)
- JWAC August 1982 [9/23], 1982 August (Box 65, Folder 6)
- JWAC August 1982 [10/23], 1982 August (Box 66, Folder 1)
- JWAC August 1982 [11/23], 1982 August (Box 66, Folder 2)
- JWAC August 1982 [12/23], 1982 August (Box 66, Folder 3)
- JWAC August 1982 [13/23], 1982 August (Box 66, Folder 4)
- JWAC August 1982 [14/23], 1982 August (Box 66, Folder 5)
- JWAC August 1982 [15/23], 1982 August (Box 66, Folder 6)
- JWAC August 1982 [16/23], 1982 August (Box 67, Folder 1)
- JWAC August 1982 [17/23], 1982 August (Box 67, Folder 2)
- JWAC August 1982 [18/23], 1982 August (Box 67, Folder 3)
- JWAC August 1982 [19/23], 1982 August (Box 67, Folder 4)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the P&D Break Bulk Committee and Office Disputes
- JWAC August 1982 [20/23], 1982 August (Box 67, Folder 5)
- JWAC August 1982 [21/23], 1982 August (Box 67, Folder 6)
  Proceedings/Transcripts Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters
- JWAC August 1982 [22/23], 1982 August (Box 68, Folder 1)
- JWAC August 1982 [23/23], 1982 August (Box 68, Folder 2)
- JWAC November 1982 [1/24], 1982 November (Box 68, Folder 3)
  Minutes Meeting November 8-12, 1982, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1982 [2/24], 1982 November (Box 68, Folder 4)
  Main Committee, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters; Agenda Meeting November 8-12, 1982, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1982 [3/24], 1982 November (Box 68, Folder 5)
- JWAC November 1982 [4/24], 1982 November (Box 68, Folder 6)
- JWAC November 1982 [5/24], 1982 November (Box 69, Folder 1)
- JWAC November 1982 [6/24], 1982 November (Box 69, Folder 2)
- JWAC November 1982 [7/24], 1982 November (Box 69, Folder 3)
- JWAC November 1982 [8/24], 1982 November (Box 69, Folder 4)
- JWAC November 1982 [9/24], 1982 November (Box 69, Folder 5)
- JWAC November 1982 [10/24], 1982 November (Box 69, Folder 6)
- JWAC November 1982 [11/24], 1982 November (Box 70, Folder 1)
- JWAC November 1982 [12/24], 1982 November (Box 70, Folder 2)
- JWAC November 1982 [13/24], 1982 November (Box 70, Folder 3)
- JWAC November 1982 [14/24], 1982 November (Box 70, Folder 4)
- JWAC November 1982 [15/24], 1982 November (Box 70, Folder 5)
- JWAC November 1982 [16/24], 1982 November (Box 70, Folder 6)
- JWAC November 1982 [17/24], 1982 November (Box 71, Folder 1)
- JWAC November 1982 [18/24], 1982 November (Box 71, Folder 2)
- JWAC November 1982 [19/24], 1982 November (Box 71, Folder 3)
- JWAC November 1982 [20/24], 1982 November (Box 71, Folder 4)
- JWAC November 1982 [21/24], 1982 November (Box 71, Folder 5)
- JWAC November 1982 [22/24], 1982 November (Box 72, Folder 1)
  72-1, 22/24, Transcripts/Proceedings of the Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC November 1982 [23/24], 1982 November (Box 72, Folder 2)
- JWAC November 1982 [24/24], 1982 November (Box 72, Folder 3)
- JWAC February 1983 [1/22], 1983 February (Box 72, Folder 4)
  Agenda Meeting February 14-18, 1983, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Break Bulk Committee, Main Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters, O-T-R Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1983 [2/22], 1983 February (Box 72, Folder 5)
  Break Bulk Committee, Main Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1983 [3/22], 1983 February (Box 73, Folder 1)
  Minutes Meeting February 14-18, 1983, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Break Bulk Committee, Main Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1983 [4/22], 1983 February (Box 73, Folder 2)
  Agenda Meeting February 14-18, 1983, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters, Joint Council # 7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1983 [5/22], 1983 February (Box 73, Folder 3)
  Break Bulk Committee, Main Committee, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1983 [6/22], 1983 February (Box 73, Folder 4)
- JWAC February 1983 [7/22], 1983 February (Box 73, Folder 5)
- JWAC February 1983 [8/22], 1983 February (Box 73, Folder 6)
- JWAC February 1983 [9/22], 1983 February (Box 74, Folder 1)
- JWAC February 1983 [10/22], 1983 February (Box 74, Folder 2)
- JWAC February 1983 [11/22], 1983 February (Box 74, Folder 3)
- JWAC February 1983 [12/22], 1983 February (Box 74, Folder 4)
- JWAC February 1983 [13/22], 1983 February (Box 74, Folder 5)
- JWAC February 1983 [14/22], 1983 February (Box 74, Folder 6)
- JWAC February 1983 [15/22], 1983 February (Box 75, Folder 1)
- JWAC February 1983 [16/22], 1983 February (Box 75, Folder 2)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the Break Bulk Committee
- JWAC February 1983 [17/22], 1983 February (Box 75, Folder 3)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the Committee for Local Operations
- JWAC February 1983 [18/22], 1983 February (Box 75, Folder 4)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the Alternate Main Committee
- JWAC February 1983 [19/22], 1983 February (Box 75, Folder 5)
- JWAC February 1983 [20/22], 1983 February (Box 75, Folder 6)
  Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters
- JWAC February 1983 [21/22], 1983 February (Box 76, Folder 1)
- JWAC February 1983 [22/22], 1983 February (Box 76, Folder 2)
- JWAC May 1983 [1/26], 1983 May (Box 76, Folder 3)
  Original forms filed with Joint Council #7 Labor Management Committee, Agenda Meeting May 9-13, 1983, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Main Committee, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1983 [2/26], 1983 May (Box 76, Folder 4)
  Minutes Meeting May 9-13, 1983, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Break Bulk Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1983 [3/26], 1983 May (Box 76, Folder 5)
- JWAC May 1983 [4/26], 1983 May (Box 76, Folder 6)
  Minutes Meeting May 9-13, 1983, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Break Bulk Committee, Main Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1983 [5/26], 1983 May (Box 77, Folder 1)
  Agenda Meeting May 1983, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1983 [6/26], 1983 May (Box 77, Folder 2)
- JWAC May 1983 [7/26], 1983 May (Box 77, Folder 3)
- JWAC May 1983 [8/26], 1983 May (Box 77, Folder 4)
- JWAC May 1983 [9/26], 1983 May (Box 77, Folder 5)
- JWAC May 1983 [10/26], 1983 May (Box 77, Folder 6)
- JWAC May 1983 [11/26], 1983 May (Box 78, Folder 1)
- JWAC May 1983 [12/26], 1983 May (Box 78, Folder 2)
- JWAC May 1983 [13/26], 1983 May (Box 78, Folder 3)
- JWAC May 1983 [14/26], 1983 May (Box 78, Folder 4)
- JWAC May 1983 [15/26], 1983 May (Box 78, Folder 5)
- JWAC May 1983 [16/26], 1983 May (Box 78, Folder 6)
- JWAC May 1983 [17/26], 1983 May (Box 79, Folder 1)
- JWAC May 1983 [18/26], 1983 May (Box 79, Folder 2)
- JWAC May 1983 [19/26], 1983 May (Box 79, Folder 3)
- JWAC May 1983 [20/26], 1983 May (Box 79, Folder 4)
- JWAC May 1983 [21/26], 1983 May (Box 79, Folder 5)
- JWAC May 1983 [22/26], 1983 May (Box 79, Folder 6)
- JWAC May 1983 [23/26], 1983 May (Box 79, Folder 7)
- JWAC May 1983 [24/26], 1983 May (Box 80, Folder 1)
- JWAC May 1983 [25/26], 1983 May (Box 80, Folder 2)
- JWAC May 1983 [26/26], 1983 May (Box 80, Folder 3)
- JWAC August 1983 [1/26], 1983 August (Box 80, Folder 4)
  Agenda, Minutes Meeting August 15-19, 1983, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Main Committee, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1983 [2/26], 1983 August (Box 80, Folder 5)
- JWAC August 1983 [3/26], 1983 August (Box 80, Folder 6)
  Minutes Meeting August 15-19, 1983, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations and Joint Council #7 Disputes, Main Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1983 [4/26], 1983 August (Box 81, Folder 1)
  O-T-R Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters, Agenda Meeting August 15-19, 1983, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations and Joint Council #7 Disputes, Break Bulk Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1983 [5/26], 1983 August (Box 81, Folder 2)
  Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations and Joint Council #7 Disputes, Break Bulk Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1983 [6/26], 1983 August (Box 81, Folder 3)
  Main Committee, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters, Minutes Meeting August 15-19, 1983, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1983 [7/26], 1983 August (Box 81, Folder 4)
  Committee for Local Operations and Joint Council #7 Disputes, Break Bulk Disputes, Main Committee, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1983 [8/26], 1983 August (Box 81, Folder 5)
- JWAC August 1983 [9/26], 1983 August (Box 81, Folder 6)
- JWAC August 1983 [10/26], 1983 August (Box 82, Folder 1)
- JWAC August 1983 [11/26], 1983 August (Box 82, Folder 2)
- JWAC August 1983 [12/26], 1983 August (Box 82, Folder 3)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the Break Bulk Committee, O-T-R Committee
- JWAC August 1983 [13/26], 1983 August (Box 82, Folder 4)
- JWAC August 1983 [14/26], 1983 August (Box 82, Folder 5)
- JWAC August 1983 [15/26], 1983 August (Box 82, Folder 6)
- JWAC August 1983 [16/26], 1983 August (Box 83, Folder 1)
- JWAC August 1983 [17/26], 1983 August (Box 83, Folder 2)
- JWAC August 1983 [18/26], 1983 August (Box 83, Folder 3)
- JWAC August 1983 [19/26], 1983 August (Box 83, Folder 4)
- JWAC August 1983 [20/26], 1983 August (Box 83, Folder 5)
- JWAC August 1983 [21/26], 1983 August (Box 83, Folder 6)
  83-6, 21/26, Proceedings/Transcripts of the Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC August 1983 [22/26], 1983 August (Box 84, Folder 1)
- JWAC August 1983 [23/26], 1983 August (Box 84, Folder 2)
- JWAC August 1983 [24/26], 1983 August (Box 84, Folder 3)
- JWAC August 1983 [25/26], 1983 August (Box 84, Folder 4)
- JWAC August 1983 [26/26], 1983 August (Box 84, Folder 5)
- JWAC November 1983 [1/20], 1983 November (Box 84, Folder 6)
  Minutes Meeting November 14-18, 1983, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations and Joint Council #7 Disputes, Break Bulk Disputes, Main Committee, O-T-R Committee, Discharges, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1983 [2/20], 1983 November (Box 84, Folder 7)
- JWAC November 1983 [3/20], 1983 November (Box 85, Folder 1)
- JWAC November 1983 [4/20], 1983 November (Box 85, Folder 2)
- JWAC November 1983 [5/20], 1983 November (Box 85, Folder 3)
- JWAC November 1983 [6/20], 1983 November (Box 85, Folder 4)
- JWAC November 1983 [7/20], 1983 November (Box 85, Folder 5)
- JWAC November 1983 [8/20], 1983 November (Box 86, Folder 1)
- JWAC November 1983 [9/20], 1983 November (Box 86, Folder 2)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the O-T-R Committee, Proceedings/Transcripts of the Break Bulk Committee
- JWAC November 1983 [10/20], 1983 November (Box 86, Folder 3)
- JWAC November 1983 [11/20], 1983 November (Box 86, Folder 4)
- JWAC November 1983 [12/20], 1983 November (Box 86, Folder 5)
- JWAC November 1983 [13/20], 1983 November (Box 86, Folder 6)
- JWAC November 1983 [14/20], 1983 November (Box 87, Folder 1)
- JWAC November 1983 [15/20], 1983 November (Box 87, Folder 2)
- JWAC November 1983 [16/20], 1983 November (Box 87, Folder 3)
- JWAC November 1983 [17/20], 1983 November (Box 87, Folder 4)
- JWAC November 1983 [18/20], 1983 November (Box 87, Folder 5)
- JWAC November 1983 [19/20], 1983 November (Box 87, Folder 6)
- JWAC November 1983 [20/20], 1983 November (Box 88, Folder 1)
- JWAC January 1984, 1984 January (Box 88, Folder 2)
- JWAC February 1984 [1/28], 1984 February (Box 88, Folder 3)
  Agenda, Minutes, Meeting February 13-17, 1984, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Main Committee, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1984 [2/28], 1984 February (Box 88, Folder 4)
- JWAC February 1984 [3/28], 1984 February (Box 88, Folder 5)
  Agenda, Minutes Meeting February 1984, Main Committee, O-T-R Committee, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee Local Operations, Joint Council #7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1984 [4/28], 1984 February (Box 89, Folder 1)
  Minutes Meeting February 13-17, 1984, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee Local Operations, Joint Council #7 Disputes, Break Bulk Disputes, Main Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1984 [5/28], 1984 February (Box 89, Folder 2)
  Change of Operations, Local Operations, Joint Council #7 Disputes, Break Bulk Disputes, Main Committee, O-T-R Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1984 [6/28], 1984 February (Box 89, Folder 3)
- JWAC February 1984 [7/28], 1984 February (Box 89, Folder 4)